Hello friends, welcome to your own
YouTube channel PSC Coaching Center.
Friends, if you are one such person and are a Common
Service Center operator, then there is great news for you.
Friends, it has started
releasing all the pending payments.
So, in today's video, we will
discuss which payments have been
released and which pending payments will
come. Everything will be
clear in this video. Let's start and
find out which
payments have been released and which ones are going to be
released which were pending.
But before that, if you
are on the target, then you are requested to
subscribe to this channel because
from here you get news of CHC every moment,
so
you get the first information about any government scheme.
Let's start and know that the
biggest boot has been used by CSE and
which payments have been released.
Send it.
Hello
friends, there is great news for all of you. It has released all the
rest.  The payments have
started being released,
even the pending payments have
started being released.
Almost all the pending payments of people have started coming
and you will have to wait for a few days. Within one to
four days, all your remaining payments will come.
Friends, before this I made a video in
which I told that your PMG
Disha payment has come. After that, your
English hum got cut and deleted somewhere. When
I made this video, many
Delhi brothers asked, Sir,
when will the remaining payment of PMG Disha come? Let me
tell you that the remaining payment of PM Vigilance,
which is trending intimately, has been released today.
No, your
credit card has been made valid in your account.
You can check your payment of PM Vigilance,
see, I took it earlier, it has come. Similarly,
if any other daughter's
payment is pending, then the payment will come very soon
in the middle of the
month of October. What will happen to the payment of Shramik Card,
you will get the payment in the middle of a big date. So, this is a big good
news for you that all the remaining
payments have started.  You do not need to
worry about clearing any payment for any work,
you just do the work that is asked for,
all your payment will come, so
let's go, payment in the next video, till then
thank you, Jai Hind, Jai Bharat, Jai Bhim friends.